You haven't seen anything yet.
Now You See Me 2 is a thriller, crime film directed by Jon M. Chu.
One year after outwitting the FBI and winning the public’s adulation with their mind-bending spectacles, the Four Horsemen resurface
only to find themselves face to face with a new enemy who enlists them to pull off their most dangerous heist yet.
J. Daniel Atlas, played by Jesse Eisenberg.
Dylan Rhodes, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Merritt McKinney / Chase McKinney, played by Woody Harrelson.
Jack Wilder, played by Dave Franco.
Walter Mabry, played by Daniel Radcliffe.
Lula, played by Lizzy Caplan.
Now You See Me 2 (also known as Now You See Me: The Second Act)
is a 2016 American heist film directed by Jon M.
Chu from a screenplay by Ed Solomon and a story by Solomon and Peter Chiarelli.
It serves as a sequel to Now You See Me (2013) and the
second installment in the Now You See Me series.
The film stars an ensemble cast that includes Jesse Eisenberg, Mark Ruffalo, Woody Harrelson, Dave Franco,
Daniel Radcliffe, Lizzy Caplan, Jay Chou, Sanaa Lathan, Michael Caine, and Morgan Freeman.
The plot has the Four Horsemen and their leader Dylan Rhodes recruited by
Walter Mabry, a criminal mastermind, to steal a data chip.
In July 2013, the film was officially announced to be in development.
Filming began in November 2014 and lasted until May 2015.
The film was released on June 10, 2016, by Lionsgate.
It received mixed reviews from critics, but was a commercial
success and grossed $334 million worldwide.
A sequel, Now You See Me: Now You Don't, was released on November 14, 2025.
The film explores themes of prison, new york city, magic, kidnapping, fbi.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending and intense.